Finding Aid for Martin Mayman papers, 1945-1997
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Menninger Clinic
  - Psychopathology Syndromes, 1945-1957 (Box 7)
  - Research in Alcoholism, 1946 (Box 7)
  - Rorschach Correspondence, 1960-1966 (Box 7)
  - "Section level teaching activities by clinical psychology staff members at Topeka State Hospital and Winter Veterans Administration Hospital, 1961 (Box 7)
  - Sentence Completion Test, 1959 (Box 7)
  - Super Ego, 1950 (Box 7)
  - Symposium, A Psychoanalyst and a methodologist look at two examples of psychoanalytic research, 1965 (Box 7)
  - TAT Testing, 1962 (Box 7)
  - Topeka Institution for Psychoanalysis, 1962-1971 (Box 7)
  - "Two Aspects of Psychoanalysis" by H.G. van der Waals, undated (Box 7)
  - W Scoring for the Oral Aggressive Study, 1955 (Box 7)
  - Wednesday evening club, 1964 (Box 7)
- UM Psychological Clinic
  UM Psychological Clinic series contains papers related to the overall functioning of the Psychology Clinic including correspondence, committee minutes and reports, budgets, program evaluations, testing guidelines, and research proposals. The series also contains materials related to institutions associated with the Clinic, such as the Detroit Psychiatric Institute, the Michigan Psychoanalytic Institute, and the Michigan Psychological Association.
  - Analysis and Evaluation of Clinic, 1977-1978 (Box 8)
  - Annual Reports, 1967-1972 (Box 8)
  - Budget, 1979-1983; 5 folders (Box 8)
  - Clinic Review, 1980-1981 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence
    - Adelson, Joe, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Doehrman, Steve, 1979 (Box 8)
    - General, 1975-1982; 3 folders (Box 8)
    - Thompson, Bill, 1976-1978 (Box 8)
  - Curriculum Review Committee, 1981-1987; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Dean Sussman meeting, 1982 (Box 8)
  - Detroit Psychiatric Institute Post-Doc Training Program, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Gender-Linked Determinants of Transference Research, 1987 (Box 8)
  - Letters of Recommendation, 1982-1988; 3 folders (Box 8)
  - Michigan Psychoanalytic Institute
    - Memos and Brochures, 1976-1979; 1997 (Box 8)
    - Reading Lists and Syllabi, 1970; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Michigan Psychological Association, 1977-1997 (Box 8)
  - Periodic Case Review Committee, 1978 (Box 8)
  - Presenting Problems Research, 1977 (Box 8)
  - Program Evaluation Clinic, 1978 (Box 8)
  - Psychotherapy Termination Research, undated (Box 8)
  - Psychological Clinic Research Reports, 1979-1985 (Box 8)
  - Quality of Life, forms and inventory, 1973; 1990 (Box 8)
  - Research Seminar, 1981-1987 (Box 8)
  - Research Support in Psychology, 1966 (Box 8)
  - Senior Staff Meeting, Minutes and Notes, 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - Therapy Outcome Research, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - UM Testing Guidelines, 1968 (Box 8)